http://www.collegenannies.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Statement
College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors ("CNT", "We", "Us" or "Our") respects and understands the importance of privacy and security for our customers. Any information collected via this website or as a result of business dealings is used only by independently owned franchise companies of College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors to contact consumers and applicants for marketing and operational purposes. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers or e-mail addresses on-line may receive telephone or e-mail contact from and independently owned and operated College Nannies and Tutors franchise with information regarding special promotions, new products and services or upcoming events. College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors will not release, sell, rent or trade the personal information of any of our customers to any third party. If you disagree with the manner in which we intend to use the Personal Information you provide to us, you may opt out of these uses by following the instructions below. By using our Site, you agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy in effect, at that time.
Information We Collect
We collect both Personal Information and non-personally identifiable information through this Site and our business dealings in order to help us to learn more about how our visitors use this Site, to measure areas of interest, and to provide our users with important information on our company and our services. Collection of information allows us to build features and functionality that will enhance your experience. You are not obligated to provide us with Personal Information in order to use the Site. However, we do require that you register and provide certain Personal Information in order to send us inquiries, to access certain restricted pages of our Site, to receive confidential information about our company and to inquire about becoming a franchisee, and to receive newsletters and other special offers. We collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of General Tracking Information and Click Path Tracking (cookie technology) described below.
Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information
1.) General Tracking InformationWe keep track of the pages visited by each user. Our web server automatically collects some information about you when you request pages from our server, including your IP address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. We aggregate this data with data on the pages visited by other users to track overall visitor traffic patterns. We use this information to improve our Site by making it more responsive to the needs and preferences of our users. This information does not identify you personally.
2.) Click Path Tracking"Cookies" are pieces of information that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with our website. Using cookie technology, we track your click path through our Site. Though this information does not identify you personally, we may use it to help customize your visit to our Site. We may also use cookies to record how many times a user has visited our Site and what pages the user has accessed. You may, however, disallow receiving cookies at any time through your web browser. It is not our intention to use cookies to retrieve information that is unrelated to our Site or your interaction with our Site.
3.) Collection of Personal InformationIf you choose to register on our Site, you will be asked to provide Personal Information which may include your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and phone number. We do not actively share Personal Information gathered from our Web servers. When you register, we will place your name in our mailing list and will send you an e-mail to the address you have provided to confirm your registration on our Site.
4.) What We Do with the Personal Information We CollectWe require Personal Information from you in order to learn more about how you use the Site; to measure areas of interest in our company and the services we provide; to understand the needs of our customers; to provide you with better service; and to help us with internal record keeping. If you register, your registration information may be used by College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors and our franchisees for internal research purposes and may be compiled as part of our internal database system. In addition, we may send correspondence to the e-mail and/or street address you provide to us when registering on our Site. This correspondence may include newsletters, promotional offers, information on new features and services we provide, Site updates, responses to your e-mails, comments and opinions, and may also be used as a means of providing technical support. In certain instances you will have an opportunity to limit these uses at the time your Personal Information is collected. You also may limit the correspondence by requesting an "Opt-Out" in response to communication.
5.) Sharing of Personal InformationWe will not provide or sell any Personal Information to marketing research or bulk advertising sales companies. We may share your Personal Information with third-party business partners who offer services in conjunction with those of College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors and who we believe may provide offers that may be of interest to you. As described above, you may limit this sharing by "Opting-Out" to any communications. We may also disclose Personal Information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may have breached our Terms of Use, or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other website users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We reserve the right to disclose your Personal Information to law-enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law. In any of these situations, registered users will be notified by e-mail of our intent to disclose information.
Links to Third Party Websites
Occasionally we may include on our Site a hyperlink (a "Link") or a banner advertisement ("Banner Ad") containing a Link which allows you to connect to the home page of third party website ("Third Party Site"), or the website of an Affiliate ("Affiliate Site"). College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors provides these Links to you as a convenient method of accessing information that may be useful or of interest to you. This Privacy Policy and the practices that we follow under this Privacy Policy do not apply to Third Party Sites or Affiliate Sites which are operated independently from College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy, or opinions expressed on any Affiliate Site or Third Party Site or for the privacy practices of our Affiliates or any third party. We will not, and are under no obligation to, investigate, monitor or check the Affiliate Sites or Third Party Sites for accuracy or completeness, or for any obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic, indecent, profane, defamatory or unlawful content or materials. Inclusion of any Link or Banner Ad to a Third Party Site or Affiliate Site that is placed on our Site does not imply approval or endorsement of the Third Party Site or Affiliate Site. You understand and agree that by clicking on a Link to a Third Party Site or Affiliate Site, you have left this Site, and the College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors Privacy Policy stated on this Site is no longer in effect.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your Personal Information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Opt-Out
You may choose to have your name taken off of our registration list, cease receiving correspondence from us; or you update the Personal Information that you have provided to us, via one of the following methods:
Using the opt-out option in e-mails you receive from us;
Sending us an e-mail at: info@collegenannies.com;
Writing to us at:College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors6465 Wayzata BlvdSuite 250Minneapolis, MN 55426
Or Calling us at: 952.476.0262
You understand that by terminating your registration that you will no longer have access to certain secured pages of our Site.
Disclaimer
The data contained in our Site is for informational purposes only and is not represented to be error free. College Nannies and Tutors attempts to ensure that the data provided or otherwise displayed on our Site is accurate. However, the Site and its contents are provided on an "as is, as available" basis. Use of the Site and its contents is at your sole risk. College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors does not warrant that any functions of the Site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the Site will be free from viruses or other harmful components. College Nannies + Sitters + Tutors makes no warranties, either express or implied, concerning the content of such site, including the accuracy, completeness, reliability or suitability of such site.
Guidelines for Children
It is our policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. We do not specifically collect information about children nor market our products or services to children. We have no reason to believe that this Site will attract children, or that children will access this Site or provide Personal Information.
Termination of Use
You agree that we may, in our sole discretion, terminate or suspend your access to all or any part of the Site with or without notice and for any reason. Any suspected fraudulent, abusive or illegal activity may be grounds for terminating our relationship, and if we believe that you have committed such acts, we may report you to appropriate law enforcement authorities.
Contact Information
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact:
College Nannies & Tutors Development, Inc.6465 Wayzata BlvdSuite 250Minneapolis, MN 55426952.476.0262dataprivacy@collegenannies.comdataprivacy@collegetutors.com
